hellobar.co.uk 2003-08-10

# Dating Services UK Online Internet Dating Service Introductions

**Hello Bar Privacy Policy**

**Coming Soon**

**1\. Information Collected**  
When you register as a member and set up a profile certain information is required. This includes personally identifiable information such as your name and email address. This information is stored on our systems, but NO personally identifiable information is ever displayed in your public profile or included in any communication between members sent via the site.

**2\. Updating Your Information**  
You can freely update all of your personal information including username, email address, location, password and all profile details. We encourage you to keep your details and photos up to date.

**3\. Your Password**  
It is vital that your keep your password safe to prevent unauthorised access to your personal information. If you believe that your password has been compromised for any reason please CHANGE it immediately.

**4\. Deleting Your Information**  
You have the option to delete your profile. Please note that this permanently deletes all your information. No data will remain in the database and should you wish to renew your membership a new account would need to be set up.

**5\. Personal Correspondence**  
Correspondence sent to us including emails and letters will be stored on file with access limited to our authorised staff members.

**6\. Disclosure of Your Information**  
We will not disclose any of your information without your permission.   
We will not supply any member's details to any other member.   
We will not give your information to any third party.   
We will only disclose your information if legally obligated to do so. 

**7\. No Spam Policy  
**You will receive emails from us and emails from other members. However, we will never supply your email address to any third party.

**8\. Internal Use of Information**  
We may internally use your information to improve our services, analyze site usage, optimise content, etc. This will only be conducted by authorised staff members. We may use personally identifiable information to troubleshoot problems and implement our terms and conditions.

**9\. Security**  
Our technical team will do their utmost to ensure the security of our systems. Internet Security is a complex topic and no system can be considered 100% secure. Should a security breach occur we would endeavor to react as fast as possible to remedy the problem. However we cannot assume responsibility for member details compromised in the unlikely event of a security breach.

**10\. Changes to This Policy**  
If we make material changes to our privacy policy, these changes will be posted here and emailed to current members.
